Smbat Voskanyan ▶ Portfolio ♀ Git in Linkedin ■ smbat@duck.com ■ (46) 764461812

Game programmer with an interest in ray tracing, optimization, technical art, and low-level graphics. I have extensive experience in software engineering and computer science. Contributed to different successful projects varying from game development to web apps. Studied arts and shipped all projects with a nice touch and unique style. Technology geek and enthusiast, a gamer at heart.

Professional Experience

Rockbite Games

Mid Game Developer+

Yerevan, Armenia Sep 2020 – Jul 2023

Games <u>Deep Town</u>, <u>Sandship</u>, <u>Battle Cards</u>, <u>Idle Humans</u>, <u>Idle Outpost</u>, <u>Metropolis Tycoon</u>. Developed complex UI and gameplay with LibGDX and Java. Contributed to in-house and open-source engine <u>Talos</u>. Game Design team. Led R&D for a playable advertisements engine. Analytics and marketing tools.

.....

Jul 2019 – Sep 2019 Beeline Mar 2017 – Nov 2017 Aparg Yerevan, Armenia Yerevan, Armenia Senior Front End Developer Service Digitization team Worked on Cincopa and Shazoom.io. Vanilla JS, Supported Service Digitization, Design, and browser extensions, Web Workers, MediaDevices, Marketing. Converting products and services for and Media Stream. online accessibility. Twice awarded as the employee of the month Jun 2017 – Aug 2017 FlyCode LLC FlvCode LLC Jun 2016 – Aug 2016 Yerevan, Armenia Yerevan, Armenia Junior Full Stack Web Developer Junior Front End Web Developer

Web apps with HTML5, CSS (Less), JS (Angular JS), NodeJS (Express.js, Socket.io), MongoDB.

Web apps with HTML5, CSS (Less), JavaScript (Angular JS)

Technical Skills

- C/C++ OpenGL/WebGL Ray Tracing Implementing White Papers Java LibGDX
- ECS OOP Godot Blender Linear Algebra JS/ES6 Sql/NoSql DBs Linux/Unix
- GLSL Git Node.js Pixi.js TypeScript Public speaking Communication

Education

Uppsala University: Campus Gotland

MFA in Game Design

American University of Armenia

BS in Computer Science

Tumo Center for Creative Technologies

Programming, Web Dev, Game Dev, Graphics Design, Music Prod, Swift and XCode, and ML. Also, trained TUMO students as a TA for the Programming workshop.

Hakob Kojoyan Educational Complex

Art high school. In parallel to general subjects, took art classes such as painting, design, sculpting, art history, and mythology.

Volunteer Experience

- WCIT 2019 Yerevan, Armenia (Oct 2019): Volunteer in help-center team and co-leader
- <u>TUMO Summer Camp</u> Yerevan, Armenia (Summer 2019): TA for programming workshop
- Avo! Yerevan, Armenia (Dec 2017 Mar 2019): Participated in almost all their charity events and programs organized in the specified period, helping with organizational work and many other tasks

Certifications

• Fundamentals of Accelerated Computing with CUDA C/C++, Nvidia

Jun 22, 2022